Contact

73 Charlie Van Breda Drive 063 341 07777 (Mobile) shaun.c.jonker@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shaunjonker-097914182 (LinkedIn) shaun-jonker.github.io/My-Portfolio/ (Personal) github.com/Shaun-Jonker (Other)

Top Skills

JavaScript

HTML

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Afrikaans (Full Professional)
Dutch (Limited Working)

Certifications

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structure

The Complete Java Certification Course

Shaun Jonker

Web Developer at Sure Web Dev | JavaScript | HTML | CSS | MongoDB | Frontend & Backend

Somerset West Area, South Africa

Summary

I caught the coding bug!

It all started one day when playing Minecraft (Yes I love Minecraft). I thought of a feature that would be nice to add to the game but found that no one had made such a plugin.

So I decided how hard could it be and decided to make it myself. I first saw how some were made and found it immediately interesting and something clicked when I saw all of this confusing writing and decided to learn what it all meant. As I started going through video after video and as I eventually learned how to write Java I said to myself "I want more".

So I studied HTML then CSS some CSS libraries, JavaScript and its libraries such as BootStrap, Jquery, Handlebars.js, Angular.js, Node.js etc. Then my thoughts were why stop there? So I studied to become a Full Stack Developer.

I truly love this career and I'm not looking back. I wish I had found this passion sooner...

My specialties include quickly learning skills and programming languages, problem-solving, responsive design principles, website optimizations, OOP. I am still enthusiastically grabbing onto any other programming languages, frameworks, or principles I can integrate into my work...

Keys skills -HTML CSS Sass JavaScript Bootstrap Handlebars.js

Angular.js

Vue.js

MongoDB

Git/GitHub

Experience with SEO

Managerial Skills

team leader

Quality Customer Service

Experience

Sure Web Dev Web Developer

November 2019 - Present

South Africa

Freelance Web Developer for small businesses.

ABC360

English Teacher

May 2014 - November 2019 (5 years 7 months)

Hong Kong

Provided quality teaching and improving overall student pass rate at school.

Prepared curriculum to suit the student's needs.

Jimmy The Fish

Head Chef

January 2013 - January 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Stellenbosch

Worked in a high paced environment to meet deadlines.

Produced high-quality service with consistency.

Cut spending of the kitchen by 12%.

Trained staff on kitchen cleanliness.

Wilberry (Pty) Ltd t/a Eco Wash

Field Supervisor

April 2009 - January 2011 (1 year 10 months)

Durban Area, South Africa

Maintained quality control through all franchises throughout the country.

Pro Clean Car Valet

Manager

June 2006 - January 2009 (2 years 8 months)

Stellenbosch

Handled customer orders.

Paid monthly salaries.

Quality control of vehicles returned to customers.

Education

Shaw Academy

Diploma, Photography · (2015 - 2016)

Global TEFL

diploma, Teaching English as a Second or Foreign Language/ESL Language Instructor \cdot (2013 - 2014)

The Hurst Campus

Diploma, Culinary Arts/Chef Training · (2011 - 2013)

Paul Roos Gimnasium/Gymnasium

· (2002 - 2007)